Candice Duncan

Stockport | 07952 983530 | candy125dncn@gmail.com

Personal Summary:

A highly ambitious, motivated individual who can bring passion, drive, performance, excellence and a winning mentality to any company.

I have a clear, logical mind with a practical approach to problem solving and a drive to see things to completion. With previous experience in managing and leading teams across the Information Technology sector. I am a person who can communicate clearly and effectively when working with people of all levels. With a proven work history, I am prepared to work above and beyond to deliver and exceed expectations.

Education:

The Knowledge Academy, Manchester PRINCE 2© Foundation and Practitioner

September 2018

Nelson Mandela Metropolitan University, South AfricaDiploma in IT Software Development

Graduated 2015

Alexander Road High School, South Africa

2005 - 2009

Matric Grade 12 including Mathematics, English, ICT & Business.

Career history:

Evo – soft Limited, Denton, Manchester Junior Project Manager Project Coordinator

April 2019 – Present August 2017 – March 2019

Responsibilities:

- Ensuring the overall success of a project from initiation, planning and design, to monitoring and controlling throughout the project to ensure project closure.
- Support and co-ordinate a team of consultants and liaise with the development teams.
- Organise and chair meetings; ensure that the relevant matters are discussed, and effective decisions are made and carried out.
- Preparing meeting agendas, minutes, project documentation such as; Functional Requirement Documents, Gantt charts etc.
- Account management, building relationships with customers.
- Co-ordinate and manage project workshops, agree objectives and functional requirements.

- Liaise with solution specialists and consultants to define and document the project requirements and activities.
- Identify resources and work with the Project Manager and Resource Manager to assign responsibilities for the projects and tasks.
- Create, deliver and revise project work plans as appropriate to meet changing needs and requirements.
- Breakdown projects into doable actions and work packages, set timeframes and manage day-to-day operational aspects of the projects.
- Support the build, delivery, review and testing software modules and manage sign-off activities.
- Ensure project documents are complete, current and appropriately stored and shared.
- Manage project budget and resources meeting cost and time objectives.
- Work closely with relevant stake holders to help ensure effective and efficient implementation of the projects.
- Regularly review project status and submit reports to stakeholders and highlight any required and relevant corrective action.
- Be risk and opportunity aware, and take ownership of tasks, manage and monitor through to conclusion.

Corinium Care / Patricia Whites - Care AssistantVarious locations

February 2015 – July 2017

Rome Restaurant – Bar Supervisor South Africa **August 2008 – February 2012**

Additional Information:

First aid certificate
Full UK driving license, clean

References:

Available upon request.